Denise Weber

Uniontown, OH 44685 dweber0001@gmail.com (330) 212-1204

Personal Summary

I am making a career change after working in the medical records field for many years. After my team was laid off due to offshoring, I was offered the option of pursuing an associate degree in software development, which I pursued wholeheartedly! I am excited for the opportunity to utilize the skills I have learned, and have a strong desire to continue learning and grow as a web developer. I am an independent learner, can handle multiple tasks and pressure as evidenced by my year-round full-time online degree, as well as prior work history in a remote independent environment. I have an upbeat, positive demeanor, and am passionate about learning and technology. I am seeking an entry level position to begin my career in web development. I am persistent, if I don't understand something I will research to find the answers, if stuck I will ask for help. I work hard and I am looking for a long-term commitment.

Work Experience

Quality Improvement Specialist (Remote position)

MModal (formerly MedQuist) - Franklin, TN

October 2008 to October 2018

Responsibilities: Drive Service Delivery excellence for assigned customers via compliance with Quality Program. Duties: Train and mentor MT/QA staff and international labor partners to consistently attain quality goals utilizing live audits and positive communication. Perform monthly assigned MT and customer quality audits. Due to offshoring, my entire team was laid off October 2018.

Manager, Service Delivery (Remote position)

MModal (formerly MedQuist) - Franklin, TN

July 2007 to October 2008

Managed 5 SD Supervisors and staff of 600 MTs, 45 QA Staff. Daily Goals: Train/Support Supervisors to achieve workflow and quality goals, address stat issues, hiring, training, PMP/PIP, termination. Ongoing Goals: Responsible for performance of Supervisors, MTs and QA staff in attaining turnaround times, quality and customer service goals for the 105 hospitals/clinics in our book of business. Company restructure resulted in elimination of all Manager Roles, I was retained and moved to position of Quality Improvement Specialist.

QA Manager/Audit Supervisor (Remote position)

MModal (formerly MedQuist) - Franklin, TN

July 2003 to July 2007

Managed 32 FTE QA Specialists. Developed QA plan to address quality issues/TAT and to increase QA production. Promoted to Audit Supervisor N Region 06/2006, as part of new national team. Responsibilities: Develop, interview, hire, train team of 15 auditors. Lotus Notes Audit DB Administrator. Developed training materials, led webinars, functioned as nationwide trainer for new auditors, liaison for database users and resource for other Audit Supervisors. Promoted to Manager, Service Delivery.

Education

Associate Degree - Software Development

Sinclair Community College - Dayton, OH

Graduated with Honors. Cumulative GPA of 3.41

Certificate - IT Fundamentals 08/2020

Certificate - Fast Track Programming 12/2020

April 2019 to December 2020

MModal Management Program - Harvard Business School August 2007 to October 2008 Leadership/Coaching, Managing Performance Problems, PMP/PIP, Assessing Performance, Leading Virtual High-Performing Teams, Setting Goals, Delegating, Managing Crises, Time Management.

Links

Portfolio: https://dweber0001.github.io/ GitHub: http://github.com/dweber0001

Skills

- ASP.NET (1 year)
- CSS (2 years)
- ORACLE SQL/MySQL
- DATABASE DESIGN (ERD)
- HEROKU

- BOOTSTRAP
- HTML5 (2 years)
- PHP (< 1 year)
- FLASK
- GITHUB

- C# (1 year)
- JAVASCRIPT (1 year)
- PYTHON (< 1 year)
- JINJA2
- MongoDB

Additional Skills

- Medical records terminology, auditing, reporting, research (10+ years)
- Supervisor/Manager; team building, problem-solving, coaching, leading virtual teams, communication/time management, assessing performance, managing performance issues, PMP/PIP, hiring, training, setting goals. (5 years)
- MS Office products, research/analysis, small business accounting, QuickBooks.